<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>The Technical Writer Blog</title>
    <link>https://thetechnicalwriter.art/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Technical Writer Blog</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://thetechnicalwriter.art/papermod-cover.png</url>
      <link>https://thetechnicalwriter.art/papermod-cover.png</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 16:07:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thetechnicalwriter.art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why_doc_as_code</title>
      <link>https://thetechnicalwriter.art/post/why_doc_as_code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 16:07:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thetechnicalwriter.art/post/why_doc_as_code/</guid>
      <description>Why your org should seriously consider Doc as Code for Documentation More and more organizations are jumping on the Doc as Code train for their main documentation process. It&amp;rsquo;s pretty simple, really. Treat your documentation like code, store it and version it with your codebase, and manage it all in one place. And let me tell you, this approach has some major perks. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;re going to break down why you and your team should consider Doc as Code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://thetechnicalwriter.art/post/the-importance-of-technical-writers-in-software-documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thetechnicalwriter.art/post/the-importance-of-technical-writers-in-software-documentation/</guid>
      <description>The Importance of Technical Writers in Software Documentation In the world of software development, documentation is just as important as the code itself. Documenting a software and API allows developers to communicate with other developers, stakeholders, and end-users, ensuring that everyone understands how the software works and how to use it. But should software engineers be responsible for writing all the documentation? The short answer is no. In this article, we’ll explore the reasons why technical writers are crucial to a software development team and the documentation process.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
